Finding Aid for the Cecil Sims
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Miscellaneous. Approximately 100 items, including flyers and blurbs, application forms, lists of names and addresses, and maps of France. Also included is a holographic paragraph signed by O.W. Holmes, dated March 8, 1931. (Box 25)
Johnston, D.W., (3); Dec. 8, 1961, May 18, 1965, June 27, 1967; 8
Jones, Jesse L., (2); May 7, 1935, Oct. 25, 1940; 8
Jones, Paul, (1); July 13, 1948; 8
Jordan, Jno. A., (1); Mar. 26, 1943; 8
Joslin, G. Stanley, (1); Oct. lo, 1962 (to Estes Kefauver); 8
Julien, V., (1); Mar. 11, 1963; 8
Kahn, lsidor, (1); Sept. 28, 1939; 8
Kane, Ward, (1); July 14, 1949; 8
Keeble, David H., (2); Apr. 25, 1939, Apr. 9, 1948; 8
Keeble, Edwin~., (3); Oct. 23, 1937, Feb. 14, 1946, July 2, 1946; 8
Kefauver, Estes, (35); May 4, 1934, Apr. 15, 1949, npr. 1, 1952, Jan. 15, 1954, July 29, 1954, Aug. 11, 1954, Aug. 17, 1954, Mar. 11, 1955, Oct. 31, 1955, Nov. 14, 1955, Nov. 14, 1955(to Philip Kerrigan, Jr.), Dec. 9, 1955, Apr. 1, 1956
Kefauver, Estes, cont., My.4, 1956, May 18, 1956, Nov. 17, 1956, Mar. 21, 1957, Mar. 30, 1957, June 4, 1947, June 4, 1957, June 4, 1957 (to Herbert Brownell, Jr.), June 17, 1957, July 16, 1957, Dec. 3, 1957, Mar. 18, 1958, Jan. 29, 1959, Apr. 20, 1959, May 18, ’1959, July 2i, 1960 (to Eldan Hatcher), har. 1, 1961, May 8, 1961, May 26, 1961, July 21, 1961, Aug. 11, 1961, Oct. 11, 1961; 8
Kefauver, Nancy, (l); May 14, 1967; 8
Kell, Adeline s., (l); (n.d.) (to Miss Webb); 8
Kemp, A.N., (1); July 22, 1936; 8
Kemp, Hardy A., (l); Mar. 13, 1947 (to Michael J. Bent); 8
Keys, I.W., (4); Dec. 13, 1939, Feb. 12, 1940, June 6, 1941, Sept. 10, 1941; 9
Kiea, Michaels., (l); Dec. 7, 1954; 9
Kind Words Club, (1); May 3, 1944 (to Everett); 9
King, Earl, (1); May 2, 1934; 9
King, Joseph E.J., (1); Apr. 4, 1962; 9
Kirby, vames C. Jr., (1); Sept. 6, 1962; 9
Kirkland, J.H., (2); Oct. 1, 1932, (to L.R. Campbell), Oct. l, 1934; 9
Kirtland, l’’red, (4); June 26, 1934, July 18, 1934, July 31, 1934, Aug. 31, 1935; 9
Knodel, Don, (1); June 20, 1966; 9
Kocher, Floyd M., (1); Jan. 29, 1957; 9
Koehler, Robert H., (1); Feb. 7, 1957; 9
Koen, John, (1); Feb. 2, 1943; 9
Kraemer, Aline, (l); Feb. 1, 1957; 9
Kuhn, Edward W., (3); Jan. 11, 1955, Sept. 12, 1956, Mar. 13, 1959; 9
Lackey, Vaden Jr., (1); Jan. 2, 1962; 9
Lahr, Nie, (1); July 25, 19j3; 9
Lake, Devereux, (l); Sept. 7, 1942; 9
Lambert, Robert A., (2); Nov. 2, 1950, Nov. 2, 1950; 9
Lancaster, Jim K., (1); May 9, 1963; 9
Landis, James M., (1); Feb. 9, 1946; 9
Lanier, Sartain, (1); May 26, 1964; 9
Lansden, Dick, (1); May 11, 1960; 9
Laporte, Cloyd, (2); Apr. 21, 1937; May 11, 1937; 9
Laramie, Beatrice, (l); Dec. 7, 1960; 9
Larson, M. Berneice, (l); Sept. 25, 1948; 9
Lassiter, W.H., (1); Feb. 2, 1956; 9
Lawler, T. Newman, (l); Nov. 20, 1946 (to Stanley I. Posner); 9
Lawton, Chas. T., (1); Feb. 9, 1957; 9
Lawwell, T. Edward, (l); Mar. 8, 1962; 9
Leathers, Ala Price, (l); July 11, 1962; 9
Ledyard, Q.R. (Bob), (l); Feb. 7, 1938; 9
Lee, Robert E., (5); June 17, 1935, Mar. 27, 1936, Apr. 9, 1936, June 12, 1936, July 5, 1939; 9
Leech, William E., (l); Aug. 17, 1951; 9
Leslie, Charles K. Jr., (l); June 30, 1939; 9
Lester, Robert M., (l); Dec. 28, 1951 (to John E. Ivey); 9
Levine, Alfred T., (2); June 14, 1945 (to Ernest Spain), July 15, 1948; 9
Levy, George D., (1); Oct. 2, 1935; 9
Levy, Henry L., (l); Dec. 12, 1966; 9
Lewis, D.L. Jr., (l); Oct. 18, 1949; 9
Lewis, Fred J., (2); Feb. 22, 1946, Nov. 12, 1957 (to Overton Williams); 9
Lewis, James Hamilton, (1); May 18, 1937; 9
Lewis, Mary Dance, (l); May 13, 1933; 9
Ligon, Wister H., (l); June 22, 1962; 9
Lingner, W.H., (l); Mar. 26, 1935; 9
Litton, Louise, (l); July 21, 1950 (to Mary Mitchell); 9
Long, John R. Jr., (l); Sept. 7, 1964; 9
Long, Mahlon H., (2); Mar. 6, 1934, Mar. 31, 1936; 9
Long, Mitchell, (l); May 7, 1934; 9
Longenecker, Herbert E., (l); Aug. 28, 1961; 9
Loser, J. Carlton, (l); Apr. 18, 1962; 9
Louthan, A.V., (1); Aug. 15, 1940 (to Joseph w. Byrns, Jr.); 9
Lovell, Charles F., (5); July 26, 1939, Aug. 3, 1939, Hay 12, 1942, Apr. 6, 1943, June 4, 1948; 9
Lowder, H., (1); Feb. 5, 1945; 9
Lucy, Andre, ( 1); ( n.d. ); 9
Lucy, Veuve, (1); (n.d.); 9
Luton, Luther, (1); Feb. 15, 1946; 9
Lyle, Richard H., (1); Jan. 2, 1953; 9
McAdams, Robert E., (1); Apr. 15, 1964; 9
McAlister, Hill, (2); July 31, 1933, Apr. 25, 1935; 9
McCadden, J.E., (7); July 27, 1938, Nov. 2, 1938, Nov. 15, 1938, Nov. 15, 1938, Nov. 23, 1938, May 6, 1944, Feb. 13, 1957; 9
McCall, Howard J. Jr., (1); Dec. 31, 1940; 9
McCall, John R., (2); Sept. 27, 1966, Oct. 19, 1966; 9
McCallum, Janet, (1); Mar. 25, 1935; 9
McCanless, George F., (l); June 16, 1955 (to Quill E. Cope); 9
McClure, John, (1); Oct. 29, 1956; 9
McCord, Jim, (3); Feb. 14, 1946, Aug. 23, 1946, Oct. 14, 1949; 9
McCord, Joe P., (1); Apr. 26, 1937; 9
McCord, Leon, (1); June 12, 1947; 9
McCord, Vera, (l); Feb. 26, 1948; 9
McCorkle, Wm., (1); Sept. 20, 1935; 9
McCorry, Thomas, (1); Sept. 26, 1959; 9
McCoy, H.L., (1); Oct. 21, 1936; 9
MacCracken, William P. Jr., (1); Jan. 9, 1933; 9
McDermott, Edward A., (1); Sept. 9, 1964 (to Robert Halleck); 9
McEwen, Normans., (4); Feb. 2, 1959 (to AIF), Dec. 3, 1962, Dec. 15, 1962, Jan. 18, 1963; 9
MacFarland, ~lfred T., (1); Mar. 6, 1961; 9
McGaugh, Shirley, (3); Aug. 10, 1953, Apr. 1, 1963, (n.d.); 9
McGaw, Robert, (2); May 26, 1959, July 30, 1963; 9
McGill, Ralph, (1); July 26, 1948; 9
McGainness, H.B., (1); Apr. 2, 1954; 9
McGlothlin, W.J., (25); Oct. 18, 1948, Jan. 12, 1949, Jan. 17, 1949, Jan. 18, 1949 (to Gordon Browning), Apr. 7, 1949, May 2, 1949, May 13, 1949 (to C.E. Brehm), June l, 1949, July 6, l949,(to J.P. Hess), July 11, 1949 (to J.M. Smith), July 13, 1949 (toM. Don Clawson), Aug. 17, 1949 (to ~.E. Turner), Aug. 18, 1949 (to J.M. Smith), Oct. 10, 1949 (to Gordon Browning), Oct. 24, 1949, Nov. 11, 1949, Dec. 15, 1949, Mar. 10, 1950 (to J.M. Smith), Apr. 11, 1950 (to C.E. Brehm), Apr. 11, 1950 (tp J.M. Smith), July 20, 1950 (to Grady W. Huffman), Nov. 7, 1950 (to J.A. Barksdale), Dec.l8, 1950 (to Gordon Browning), Mar. 2, 1951, May 21, 1951 (to C.E. Brehm); 9
McGrath, J. Howard, (4); May 21, 1948, July 26, l948k Aug. 25, 1949, (n.d.); 9
McHugh, William Thomas, (l); Sept. 15, 1966; 9
Mcintyre, Henry L., (l); Feb. 18, 1942; 9
McKellar, Kenneth, (40); July 11, 1933, Apr. 4, 1934, Apr. 27, 1934, Nov. 5, 1934, July l, 1935, Aug. 5, 1935, Dec. 26, 1935, Mar. 2, 1936, May 15, 1936, May 20, 1936, Dec. 7, 1937 (to Thad A. Cox), Dec. 16, 1937 (to C.M. McCabe), Jan. 31, 1938, Mar. 15, 1938, Mar. 16, 1938 (to E.E. Murrey), Mar. 26, 1938, Nov. 18, 1938, Nov. 22, 1938, Nov. 24, 1938, Jan. 3, 1939, Jan. 7, 1939, Apr. l, 1939, Dec. 20, 1940, Mar. l, 1941, June 6, 1942, July 10, 1942, July 17, 1942, Oct. 28, 1943, Nov. 3, 1943, ~pr. 20, 1944, May 12, 1944, Oct. 29, 1944, Nov. 21, 1944, Jan. 10, 1945, Apr. 26, 1945, Sept. 3, 1945, Jan. 9, 1946, Mar. 19, 1946, June 12, 1946, Aug. l, 1951; 9
McLaughlin, Ruth, (l); Apr. 3, 1933; 9
McLemore, c.c., (l); May 12, 1933; 9
McLeod, J.H., (l); June 16, 1949; 9
McMahon, Lillian W., (l); Jan. 2, 1935; 9
McMaster, Daniel Riley, (5); Oct. 29, 1958, Nov. 8, 1958, Dec. 30, 1959, Feb. 10, 1960, Feb. 17, 1960; 9
McNeil, E.C., (l); Mar. 25, 1941; 9
McNicholas, Tom, (3); Feb. 3, 1954 (to Russell), Feb. 15, 1954 (to Silliman Evans), Mar. 3, 1954; 9
McQuiddy, David L., (1); Feb. 16, 1946; 9
McShane, B.N., (l); Oct. 19, 1964; 9
Mack, C.M., (l); Aug. 7, 1963; 9
Maddin, John K., (3); Mar. 19, 1934, Hay 5, 1934, June 25, 193?; 9
Haddox, D.D., (1); July 14, 1933; 9
Maddux, Jared, (1); Feb. 15, 1957; 9
Mager, M., (1); Mar. 22, 1945; 9
Majors, J.A., (1); Oct. 16, 1942; 9
Malone, Gayle Jr., (1); Apr. 25, 1966; 9
Malone, Mary Cornelia, (1); Aug. 25,(n.d.); 9
Maloney, Nell s., (1); Feb. 13, 1946; 9
Manier, J. Owsley, (1); July 26, 1939; 9
Mann, Burk, (1); Feb. 22, 1934; 9
Mann, Sam H., (16); May 16, 1934, June 30, 1934, Dec. 3, 1934, Jan. 7, 1935, Aug. 12, 1936, Jan. 22, 1937, Feb. 23, 1937, Nov. 29, 1937, June 17, 1940, Apr. 24, 1945, Sept. 23, 1947, Feb. 2, 1950, May 6, 1950, Feb. 12, 1957, Sept. 13, 1961, Oct. 30, 1961; 9
Marecha1, Greer, (1); May 14, 1935; 9
Marks, Louise, (1); June 19, 1948; 9
Marshall, Alfred, (1); Aug. 17, 1946; 9
Marston, George A., (1); June 13, 1939; 9
Martin, Abbott, (1); Aug. 23, 1948; 9
Martin, Joe, (1); Feb. 18, 1946; 9
Martin, John D., (4); Feb. 16, 1945, Jan. 15, 1946, May 20, 1946, May 29, 1946; 9
Maxwell, Aubrey 0., (1); Sept. 19, 1966; 9
May, A.J., (1); June 21, 1940 (to Joseph W. Byrns, Jr.); 9
May, Dan, (2); May 27, 1959, Mar. 17, 1965; 9
The Mayfields, (1); (n.d.); 9
Mayfield, U.H., (1); Nov. 2, 1949; 9
Mayfield, Lilli Hasslock, (1); May 20, 1965; 9
Mendelson, Wallace, (1); Dec. 6, 1955; 9
Merme11, Stanley,P., (1); May 23, 1955; 9
Merritt, Gilberts., Jr., (4); Aug. 2, 1961, ug. 3, 1961 (to Nicky Beehan, Jr.), Apr. 20, 1964, (to John H. Peay), Sept. 15, 1964 (to J.E. Moss); 9
Merritt, Marjorie, (1); Aug. 12, 1948; 9
Metropolitan Life Insurance Company, (2); Nov. 15, 1933 (to F.M. Bass), Nov. 15, 1933 (to F.M. Eass); 9
Middle Tennessee Electric -Membership Corporation, (1); Jan. 23, 1965; 9
Milam, Roger A., (1); Dec. 28, 1966; 9
Miles, Lovick P., (2); Oct. 11, 1937 (to R.V. Fletcher), Oct. 21, 1937 (to Ben Goodman, Jr.); 9
Miles, Roy A., (2); Feb. 28, 1963, Mar. 14, 1963; 9
Miles, W.M., (1); Nov. 5, 1957; 9
Miller, Henry H., (3); Jan. 1, 1950, Jan. 1, 1950, (n.d.); 9
Miller, Norman P., (1); Sept. 11, 1945; 9
Miller, Priestley, (2); Nov. 7, 1960, Feb. 15, 1965; 9
Miller, R. Lee, (1); Aug. 12, 1948; 9
Miller, Robert H., (1); Aug. 25, 1960; 9
Miller, William E., (5); ~ept. 28, 19)3, Sept. 28, 1953 (to Estes Kefauver), Mar. 24, 1955, May 26, 1959, Mar. 30, 1961; 9
Miller, Wm. W., (1); Jan. 8, 1958; 9
Milligan, Harry C., (1); Oct. 31, 1938; 9
Milligan, Mrs. Harry C., (1); Nov. 13; 9
Milligan, Mike, (1); Apr. 6,(to Woody); 9
Milmine, George P., (1); (n.d.); 9
Mims, Edwin, (1); Feb. 26, 1940; 9
Mims, Ella PuryeaJZ ,. ( 1); July 8, 1959; 9
Minor, Dent, (1); ~hristma~, 1946; 9
Minor, H.D., (1); Feb. 12, 1938; 9
Mitchell, Maurice, (1); May 26, 1954; 9
Moench, Ernest, (1); Jan. 16, 1947; 9
Montgomery, Marian Hardison, (1); Feb. 11, 1951; 9
Moody, Bill, (1); May 12, 1961; 9
Mooney, W.D., (1); June 28, 1939; 9
Moore, Bob, (1); hug. 23, 1933; 9
Moore, Jeanice Byrne, (1); Sept. 30, 1959; 9
Moore, Robert E., (1); Jan. 18, 1936; 9
Moore, Robert E. Jr., (2); May 26, 1934, Dec. 14, 1936; 9
Moore, Robert W., (2); June 22, 1959, Aug. 16, 1959; 9
Moran, Nancy Ann, (1); Sept. 1, 1950; 9
Morelock, G.L., (1); Sept. 24, 1929; 9
Morgan, Eddie, (3); May 21, 1960, June 2, 1960, Feb. 20, 1962; 9
Morgan, Hugh J., (1); June 4, 1960; 9
Morgan, Joe, (3); Sept. 27, 1956 (to Howard Kirksey), Apr. 19, 1957, May 3, 1957; 9
Morgan, John L., (l); Apr. 30, 1963; 9
Morgan, Leland C., (1); Jan. 17, 1957; 9
Morgan, Walter M., (4); (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.); 9
Morris, Jim, (3); Jan. 11, 1936, Apr. 7, 1936, Sept.2, 1936; 9
Morrison, Ray, (2); Feb. 4, 1935, May 28, 1935 (to Thomas H. Peebles); 9
Morrow, Tarlton, (2); Feb. 3, 1953, Feb. 25, 1957; 9
Moss, J.E., (2); Jan. 25, 1957, Aug. 17, 1964 (to Neill S. Brown); 9
Moss, William P., (38); July 6, 1933, July 10, 1933 1 Nov. 15, 1933, July 23, 1934, Aug. 28, 1934, Dec. 30, 1935, (to Mary Webb Haggard), May 25, 1936, Aug. 31, 1937, Jan. 28, 1938, Mar. 24, 1938, Apr. 2, 1938, May 21, 1938, July 18, 1939, May 8, 1939, Sept. 11 1939, Dec. 5, 1942, Apr. 1, 1943, Apr. 9, 1943, Feb. 14, 1944, Mar. 16, 1944, May 27, 1944, Mar. 17, 1945, Mar. 22, 1945, Apr. 4, 1945, Apr. 7, 1945, Mar. 23, 1946, Mar. 23, 1946 (to Hill Turner), Apr. 2, 1946, Sept. 25, 1946, Sept. 30, 1946, Oct. 2, 1946, Oct. 25, 1947, May 12, 1951, May 12, 1951 (to Gordon Browning), Jan. 7, 1953, Jan. 8, 1953, July 31, 1958, Nov. 23, 1960; 9
Motlow, Lem, (l); July 7, 1936; 9
Moynihan, Authur, (l); Sept. 19, 1936; 9
Muenter, H.F., (1); Aug. 1, 1956; 9
Munday, V.L., (2); July 27, 1933, Aug. 4, 1933; 9
Murphy, Blakely M., (1); Mar. 11, 1949; 9
Murrah, W.F., (4); Oct. 31, 1940, Sept. 11, 1961, Sept. 27, 1961, Feb. 8, 1963; 9
Murrey, J. Woodall Sr., (1); July 9, 1940; 9
Murrey, W.P., (1); Jan. 22, 1949; 9
Myers, A.B., (1); Sept. 22, 1955; 9
Myers, Rodes K., (1); Mar. 5, 1952; 9
Nance, Edwin ’l’., (1); Feb. 19, 1951; 9
Neely, Steve, (2); May 2, 1961, Oct. 4, 1965; 9
Neese, Charles u., (3); June 30, 1955, Oct. 30, 1961, Nov. 23, 1961 (to Frank Gray, Jr. ); 9
Neil, A.B., (4); Mar. 5, 1940, Mar. 16, 1946, Oct. 1, 1954, Hay 25, 1959; 9
Nelson, Charles, (4); Mar. 25, 1938, Apr. 20, 1938, Oct. 11, 1938, Aug. 11, 1939; 9
Nelson, Glen Jr., -(1); Nov. 30, 1961; 9
Nelson, Robert M., (1); June 19, 1950; 9
Nelson, William A., (1); Sept. 3, 1940; 9
Nemetz, M.M., (1); May 7, 1935; 9
Nestor, Frances Hollow, (1); Nov. 9, 1964; 9
Newman, James A., (1); Feb. 10, 1939; 9
Nichols, Edward C. Jr., (1); June 2, 1967; 9
Nichols, G.A., (1); Jan. 8, 1933; 9
Nichols, Helen, (1); July 30, 1964; 9
Niehaus, John M., (1); Jan. 19, 1948; 9
Nimitz, C.’w., (1); Sept. 11, 1940 (to Joseph W. Byrns); 9
Noland, George w., (1); Sept. 27, 1938; 9
Nooe, Roger T., (2); Feb. 15, 1946, Mar. 5, 1948; 9
Norvell, W.E. Jr., (1); Feb. 17, 1936; 9
Notgrass, Mrs. Harry G., (1); (n.d.); 9
Nowlin, W.R., (1); Feb. 17, 1948; 9
O’Brien, Lawrence F., (1); Mar. 28. 1961; 10
O’Connor, J.A. Jr., (1); Jan. 3, 1961; 10
O’Donnell, Red, (1); Aug. 5, 1940; 10
O’Mahoney, Joseph C., (1); May 18, 1937; 10
O’Neal, Hodge, (1); Jan. 16, 1957; 10
Oligiati, Rudy, (2); July 13, 1962, July 30, 1962; 10
Olshansky, Jacob M., (1); Sept. 5, 1957; 10
Orrick, .William H. Jr., (1); Feb. 3, 1964 (to John Jay Hooker, Jr.); 10
Overall, Paul M., (1); Apr. 20, 1938; 10
Ownbey, Ewell B., (1); Sept. 2, 1935; 10
Pace, Carrie M., (1); Jan. 14, 1938; 10
Palmer, Clive W., (l); Jan. 13, 1959; 10
Pappas, T.G., (l); Aug. 28, 1961; 10
Pardue, James A., (3); Mar. 29, 1958, Sept. 18, 1958, Apr. 15, 1967; 10
Pardue, L.J., (l); Sept. 11, 1941; 10
Park, Billy, (l); June 14, 1944; 10
Parker, William, (l); July 7, 1940 (to Joseph W. Byrns); 10
Parker, William A. Jr., (16); Dec. 12, 1960, Dec. 20, 1960, Jan. 17, 1962, Aug. 7, 1962, Aug. 7, 1962 (to Frank Burton, Jr.), Aug. 21, 1962, Aug. 30, 1962, Oct. 9, 1962, Apr. 15, 1963, Apr. 22, 1963, June 20, 1963, Dec. 31, 1963, Jan. 9, 1964, Mar. 24, 1965, Sept. 19, 1966, Mar. 8, 1967; 10 Parks, L.L., (3); Aug. 12, 1936, June 6, 1939, Sept. 6; 10Patterson, Giles J., (1); Aug. 13, 1936; 10 Patton, Nancy, (1); May 7, 1967; 10 Paxman, s.w., (2); Feb. 13, 1958, Mar. 26, 1958; 10
Paxson, Harry 0., (1); July 11, 1964; 10
Peacock, N.D., (1); June 21, 1949; 10
Pearce, Elwood N., (2); Nov. 19, 1940, May 15, 1946; 10
Pearson, Herbert, (5); Apr. 4, 1933, July 12, 1933, Dec. 5, 1933, Dec. 5, 1933 (to Albert H. Thomas), Jan. 9, 1934; 10 Pearson, Herron, (1); Apr. 4, 1938; 10 Pearson, Jack, (1); Apr. 24, 1934; 10 Peay, John H., (2); Mar. 30, 1964, May 6, 1964; 10 Peay, L.M., (4); May 28, 1946, Feb. 9, 1951, Apr. 28, 1960, Aug. 31, 1962; 10 Peck and Peck, (1); Sept. 18, 1943; 10 Fenderson, Lora Lee, (1); Dec. 15, 1948; 10 Peebles, J .M., (1); Jan. 11, 1945; 10 Peebles, Thos. H., (2); May 21, 1935,(to Ray Morrison), May 30, 1935; 10 Pelletier, Geo. L., (1); Oct. 4, 1934; 10 Pepper, Harry L. (l); Nov. 25, 1964; 10 Perkins, Gilbert H., (3); Jan. 31, 1934, Aug. 10, 1938, Feb. 8, 1965; 10 Perkins, Rollin M., (1); Feb. 24, 1949; 10
Peters, Glenn D., (1); Jan. 14, 1957; 10
Petrone, Eugene M., (2); Oct. 5, 1962, Oct. 18, 1962; 10
Phelps, Mina, (l); (n.d.); 10
Phillips, Elsie Young, (1); July 20, 1963; 10
Phillips, Harry, (l); Nov. 3, 1960; 10
Phillips, L. Bowman, (1); Mar. 22, 1946; 10
Pierce, Truman M., (l); Mar. 19, 1955; 10
Pilcher, Cobb, (1); July 3, 1942; 10
Pinkerton, J.C., (2); July 9, 1960, July 19, 1960; 10
Pinkerton, Joe, (l); Feb. 14, 1944; 10
Pinkerton, John D., (2); Mar. 10, 1965, Mar. 25, 1965; 10
Pogue, Province M., (2); Apr. 30, 1934, May 21, 1934; 10
Pointer, Tom W., (3); Sept. 14, 1933, Sept. 14, 1933 (to Hilary E. Howse), May 21, 1935; 10
Polk, Horace T., (l); Jan. 25, 1946 (to William Waller); 10
Porter, Phil, (2); Mar. 12, 1957, Apr. 27, 1957; 10
Posner, Stanley I., (5); Sept. 28, 1946, Nov. 4, 1946, Jan. 19, 1947, Mar. 10, 1947, Apr. 8, 1947; 10
Potter, Chas. H., (l); Mar. 8, 1933; 10
Potter, Justin, (1); Oct. 16, 1959; 10
Prevatte, M.J., (1); Oct. 30, 1950; 10
Prewitt, Alan M., (l); Nov. 26, 1962; 10
Pride, Lewis D., (2); Mar. 30, 1957, Apr. 17, 1964; 10
Priest, J. Percy, (8); Nov. 13, 1940 (to Joseph W. Byrns), Mar. 1, 1941, Apr. 17, 1941, June 1, 1942, June 17, 1943, July 8, 1953, Apr. 25, 1955, Aug. 15, 1956; 10
Proctor, E.T., (l); Oct. 27, 1942; 10
Proctor, Edwin Thomas, (l); Feb. 12, 1946; 19
Pugh, Prentice A., (1); Oct. 26, 1946; 10
Purdy, Rob Roy, (2); June 13, 1961, Apr. 4, 1963; 10
Rahl, James A., (1); Jan. 31, 1957; 10
Ramey, Cecil E. Jr., (1); Jan. 28, 1953; 10
Ramsey, Ted, (10); Apr. 11, 1955, June 27, 1955, July 5, 1955, July 12, 1955, July 15, 1955, July 19, 1955, July 20, 1955, July 25, 1955, July 29, 1955, (n.d.); 10
Rand, F.C., (1); Sept. 9, 1948; 10
Rankin, Turley, (1); Oct. 24, 1934; 10
Read, Sallie, (1); Feb. 28, 1963; 10
Reams, Hugh E., (l); Aug. 18, 1951; 10
Reece, Carroll, (1); May 18, 1955; 10
Reem, C.F., (1); Aug. 29, 1941; 10
Reeves, JosephS., (2); Mar. 27, 1937, Sept. 9, 1960; 16
Reichman, Rod, (1); (n.d.); 10
Reid, L.V., (1); Aug. 4, 1937; 10
Reid, Rayford s., (3); Jan. 21, 1937, Oct. 28, l937,(to W.J. Diehl), Oct. 3, 1937; 10
Reuss, Carl W., (1); Dec. 17, 1951; 10
Reynolds, Morgan B., (l); Sept. 28, 1964; 10
Reynolds, Robert R., (l); May 18, 1937; 10
Reynolds, W.G., (1); July 15, 1948; 10
Rhea, David Jr., (1); Jan. 26, 1959; 10
Rhea, Louise Booton, (l); Jan. 22, 1956; 10
Rice, Bradford H., (2); Oct. 26, 1964 (to Harry J. Blackman), Oct. 30, 1964 (to Harry J. Blackman); 10
Rice, Theron J., (1); Mar. 8, 1963; 10
Rich, Stanley L., (1); Feb. 22, 1933; 10
Rich, William B., (1); Apr. 16, 1957 (to Joe Morgan); 10
Richardson, Wiley M., (l); (n.d.); 10
Ricker, Olive G., (1); Oct. 19, 1933; 10
Rimmer, Mrs. J.G., (2); Feb. 11, 1960, Dec. 15, 1966; 10
Rimmer, James G., (2); Mar. 12, 1957, Mar. 12, 1957; 10
Rimmer, James G. and Laura A., (2); Sept. 28, 1956, June 17, 1957; 10
Rippy, C.D., (2); June 5, 1948, Sept. 27, 1948; 10
Robb, Felix c., (2); Dec. 2, 1950, Nov. 18, 1964; 10
Robbins, Farland, (3); June 2, 1952, Apr. 28, 1956, Jan. 18, 1957; 10
Roberts, E.C., (1); Apr. 2, 1963; 10
Robertson, D.D., (1); Feb. 18, 1946; 10
Robertson, Douglas M., (1); July 6, 1939; 10
Robertson, S.G., (2); Apr. 20, 1937 1 May 13, 1937; 10
Rocke, W.F., (1); Apr. 7, 1937; 10
Rodes, A. ~ttle, (1); June 4, 1945; 10
Rodgers, J. Woodall, (35); Sept; 24, 1936, Sept. 30, 1936, Oct. 1, 1936 (to T.J. Anderson), Oct. 2, 1936, Nov. 14, 1936, Jan. 23, 1937, May 10, 1937, June 24, 1937, Sept. 21, 1937, Oct. 18, 1937, Oct. 29, 1937, Nov. 6, 1937, Jan. 25, 1938, Feb. 22, 1938 (to Cordell Hull), Mar. 9, 1938, Apr. 4, ’ 1938, Apr. 20, 1938, Oct. 1, 1938, Nov. 9, 1938, Feb. 18, 1939, Dec. 6, 1939 (to A.G. Nichol), Dec. 19, 1939, July 29, 1940, Oct. 26, 1940, May 17, 1941, Aug. 12, 1941, Dec. 16, 1942, June 10, 1944, Aug. 6, 1945, Aug. 12, 1946, Oct. 21, 1949, Dec. 12, 1949, Oct. 31, 1951, Mar. 24, 1955, (n.d.); 10
Rodgers, Mrs. Wm., (1); Jan. 9, 1920; 10
Roger, Glenn, (1); Mar. 14, 1950; 10
Rogers, Ernest P., (1); Dec. 9, 1958; 10
Rogers, William P., (1); July 11, 1955 (to Brooks Hays); 10
Rolfe, D.T., (3); Aug. 30, 1949, Dec. 9, 1949 (to H.H. Miller), Dec. 14, 1949; 10
Rollow, Arch, (1); (n.d.); 10
Hollow, E-.W., (2); Feb. 15, 1946, July 2, 1946; 10
Root, C.D., (1); June 3, 1959; 10
Rose, Gene Allen, (1); Nov. 15, 1965; 10
Rose, Stanley D., (1); Apr. 18, 1957; 10
Rosenberg, Joseph, (1); June 21, 1933; 10
Ross, C.A., (1); Feb. 7, 1957; 10
Ross, J.L., (1); Sept. 6, 1932; 10
Ross, Minnie, (1); July.l2, 1956; 10
Rountree, J.M., (1); Oct. 29, 1954; 10
Rowland, J.W., (1); July 23, 1940; 10
Ruddiman, Stanley, (1); Apr. 16, 1937; 10
Runyon, Charles V., (2); Oct. 11, 1940 (to Joe Hatcher), Dec. 14, 1961; 10
Runyon, F.J., (1); June 14, 1940; 10
Rushing, Herschel Lee, (2); Apr. 1, 1943, (n.d.); 10
Russell, Edvard P., (1); Mar. 26, 1934; 10
Russell, Fred, (2); Feb. 27, 1960, Feb. 5, 1965; 10
Rust, Littell, (1); Oct. 29, 1965; 10
Rust, Margaret S., (1); Oct. 26, 1966; 10
Rutter, W.J., (1); Oct. 4, 1946; 10
Ryan, B.A., (1); June 8, 1962; 10
Ryan, Doris D., (1); June 17, 1949; 10
Saltsman, William H., (1); Sept. 29, 1959; 10
Samuels, Seymour, (1); Feb. 3, 1944; 10
Sander, Dora L., (1); (n.d.); 10
Sandidge, John C., (1); Jan. 26, 1954; 10
Sandlin, L.T., (1); June 29, 1938; 10
Sarratt, C. Madison, (2); Oct. 1, 1946, (n.d.); 10
Sartor, Ryan, (1); May 31, 1955; 10
Savage, Paul, (2); Apr. 24, 1940 (to Wardlaw Steele), May 24, 1940 (to Laura Whitson); 10
Schafrann, Jay H., (7); Mar. 10, 1944, Apr. 6, 1944, Sept. 25, 1946, Mar. 3, 1947, June 6, 1947, June 27, 1961, (n.d.); 10
Schnader, William A., (1); Aug. 16, 1938; 10
Schneider, J. Thomas, (3); Feb. 1, 1937, Sept. 21, 1939, Oct. 14, 1939; 10
Schutt, J.C., (2); May 24, 1961, Sept. 23, 1964; 10
Schwartz, Leo, (2); Feb. 19, 1964, Mar. 6, 1964; 10
Schwarz, J.C., (1); Sept. 8, 1937; 10
Scott, Glenn D., (1); July 16, 1956; 10
Seidman, P.F., (1); May 19, 1949; 10
Shaft, Harold D., (1); Feb. 4, 1957; 10
Shapard, John Bolton, (1); (n.d.); 10
Sharp, Vernon Jr., (2); Feb. 20, 1946, Mar. 23, 1967; 10
Shaver, J.L., (1); May 17, 1954; 10
Shearson, Hammil & Co., (1); June 19, 1959; 10
Shedd, J.G., (1); Nov. 6, 1945; 10
Sheibly, John H., (1); Sept. 28, 1964; 10
Shelley, William F., (1); Jan. 2, 1952; 10
Shelton, Hugh T., (1); Oct. 27, 1939; 10
Sherer, Harvey Jr., (1); May 5, 1935; 10
Shipp, Grace M., (1); Oct. 4, 1934; 10
Shivers, Dudley,J., (1); Mar. 7, 1933; 10
Short, Lula Wilson, (1); Jan. 2, 1933; 10
Shoulders, H.H., (2); June 12, 1939, July 24, 1939; 10
Shriver, Thomas H., (1); Sept. 15, 1965; 10
Shull, J. Malcolm, (2); Jan. 13, 1955 (to Edward W. Kuhn), Aug. 19, 1953; 10
Shute, Hautie W., (1); Apr. 2, 1947; 10
Sidwell, W. Grady, (1); Jan. 27, 1938; 10
Simmonds, James H., (1); Jan. 5, 1955; 10
Simpson, James A., (2); Sept. 22, 1961, Oct. 25, 1961; 10
Sims, A.J., (2); Feb. 5, 1949, Apr. 18, 1966; 10
Sims, Agnes, (1); Jan. 15, 1955; 10
Sims, C.M., (5); Feb. 11, 1919, Mar. 24, 1934, July 16, 1934, Oct. 20, 1934, June 23, 1942; 10
Sims, Mrs. C.M., (7); July 25, 1918, Nov. 6, 1918, Jan. 30, 1919, June 20, 1929, May 20, 1940, (n.d.), (n.d.); 10
Sims, Cecil M., (1); Jan. 12, 1944; 10
Sims, Grace, (1); July 14, 1948; 10
Sims, Joe, (1); Jan. 21, 1949; 10
Sims, John E., (1); July 20, 1948; 10
Sims, R.P., (1); July 2, 1946; 10
Sims, Ross, (3); Jan. 1, 1935, Jan. 4, 1935, Jan. 15, 1935; 10
Sims, Roy and Isabel, (1); Sept. 4, 1955; 10
Sims, Roy & Nell, (1); (n.d.); 10
Sims, Tom, (10); Mar. 8, 1933, Mar. 8, 1933 (to Sam Campbell), Mar. 31, 1934, Mar. 20, 1935, Dec. 4, 1935, Feb. 20, 1940, Apr. 7, 1941, June 22, 1943, Oct. 23, 1945, July 1, 1946; 10
Sims, Wilson (Woody), (5); Dec. 2, 1944, Aug. 2, 1950, Aug. 10, 1951, Sept. 28, 1967 (to Mrs. Cecil Sims), (n.d.); 10
Sink, George M. Jr., (2); Jan. 19, 1940, Nov. 8, 1940; 10
Skreberg, Hans, (1); Feb. 9, 1957; 10
Sloan, George A., (2); Oct. 29, 1937, Sept. 27, 1943; 10
Sloan, John T., (1); Sept. 13, 1918; 10
Smartt, H. Knox, (1); Oct. 3, 1949; 10
Smith, Alden H., (2); May 18, 1937, Mar. 25, 1959 (to Bebe Felker); 10
Smith, Bradford Jr., (1); Sept. 27, 1966; 10
Smith, C.R., (1); May 19, 1952; 10
Smith, Edward W., (2); Feb. 15, 1946, Aug. 23, 1954; 10
Smith, Glenn P., (1); Sept.2, 1944; 10
Smith, H. Laird, (1); Dec. 7, 1944 (to Wilson Sims); 10
Smith, J. Allen, (1); Jan. 31, 1957; 10
Smith, J. Frazer, (1); (n.d.); 10
Smith, J.M: (4); June 16, 1949, (to C.E. Brehm), Jan. 4, 1950 (to John E. Ivey, Jr.), Apr. 28, 1950 (to John E. Ivey, Jr.), Apr. 28, 1950 (to John E. Ivey, Jr.); 10
Smith, Kelly Miller, (2); Oct. 17, 1962, Jan. 29, 1963; 10
Smith, Powell, (1); June 24, 1939; 10
Smith, R.T., (1); Dec. 23, 1949; 10